Now, with a new set of wheels,
JoJo and crew head north from
Varanasi to the nation of Pakistan.
We're about to hit the
Indo-Pakistani border.
I guess it's time to say goodbye to India.
You know, I had mixed feelings
about the country at first, but now,
I actually kinda miss
the hustle and bustle
of Calcutta and frenetic
chaos of the Ganges.
Hmph.
I'll be coming back
again one of these days.
I owe it to Avdol to
give him a proper burial.
Mr. Avdol.
The road's getting narrower.
We're driving so slow,
idiot! Out of the way!
I'm gonna pass the guy!
Polnareff, calm down.
This four-wheel drive is great!
You know, that crazy maneuver of yours
might have just damaged that poor car.
Yeah? Your point?
I'm saying we don't need
any more trouble now.
I'm wanted because of
what happened in Varanasi.
I'd like to get across
the border in one piece.
What's up?
Why'd you stop I told you a
crash could be disastrous.
I know that just look who's standing there
Good freaking grief.
Hey long time.
No see guys got room for one more
Let's go.
Thank you so
much for watching.
I'm gonna fight it.
Revision, Superman?
I mean, come on, I'm a girl.
Soon I'll be doing girl
things like wearing a bra
and doing my nails to get
the attention of boys.
I'd look pathetic wandering around
the world when I'm that age.
This is the only chance I have to be
free and see the world. Know what I mean?
Look, I feel bad for lying about
going to see my dad in Singapore.
Well let's just forget about that.
Hey it's that car we passed.
Looks like he's in a hurry.
Let him pass. Okay.
Polnareff. Yeah.
What the hell.
What's he trying to do.
I let you pass.
Now hurry up and go already.
He's probably angry about your maneuver
and these are the consequences.
So did you get a look at
the driver's face. No.
The windows were covered in thick dust.
Couldn't see a thing.
Neither could. I.
Couldn't be.
Be very careful. Polnareff.
Now he wants me to pass.
Looks like the fools realized.
how shitty that piece of junk is.
You should've stayed behind
me the first place, dumbass!
Coming through!
What?!
Where'd that come from?! No use! Hold on!
Star Platinum!
That was close!
If it went for star
platinum's power we would
have been crushed beneath that like a tin
can He's gone where
did that blasted car go
looks like it just kept
going i think the driver
Could have been one of the
stand users then again it could
have just been some sick bastard
Of course he's one of dio's
lackeys we were almost road
killed for god's sake Then why
didn't he simply attack us with
his stand when he had the chance?
Anyway, we've got to keep
heading to Pakistan. Be on guard.
If someone comes after us again,
we'll make them eat our dust.
Damn straight.
What should we do about that truck?
Star Platinum left it a wreck
and won't be going anywhere.
That's easy.
We pretend we never saw it.
Let's get going.
He's so cool.
A roadside T-Stand
A brake would do us some
good If we take our time,
we may avoid running
into that crazy driver
What is that stuff?
Fresh sugar cane juice.
Care for a glass?
Sure, why not?
Hmm?
What?
It's him!
That car's here!
Hey!
Tell me something!
Who's the owner of that
car parked over there?
Come on, spill it!
Uh, I'm not sure, sir.
To be honest, sir, I
didn't notice it there.
Our driver isn't just going
to come out and announce it.
He's messing with us!
Yeah, then I guess this leaves us with
only one option. Right, Jotaro? Yeah.
Yeah, poor innocent bastards.
We'll just beat them all down.
Hey, Jotaro! This is crazy!
Mr. Joestar! Not you too!
Pretty suspicious mug you got
there. Was it you? Huh? Not me!
That slippery bastard just
played the lot of us didn't he?
Damn it!
Did anyone see his face?
No
What is he trying to do?
He could be just some madman with a
car or he could be trying to kill Us.
Yeah we need to take care of this crap.
I won't rest until I catch
him and get to the bottom of
Not to mention we owe him payback for
the truck that almost hit us earlier.
Damn it.
For a piece of shit.
That car can really get up and go.
That's strange.
According to the map, we should be running
parallel with train tracks or something.
Who the hell cares?
We'll catch up soon anyway.
No, that bastard!
I'm gonna nail him once
we round this curve.
A dead end! That's impossible!
Where the hell'd he go? He's gone.
Did he just drive off the cliff?
There's no way he could
cross this suspension bridge.
What?
It's him!
He keeps pushing us!
How the hell did he get behind us?
Damn!
How much horsepower is that
piece of junk running with?
Damn it!
It's like fighting a tank!
It's no use!
Everyone, get out!
It's our only chance!
Polnareff, what are you doing?
You can't get out of the car until
the rest of us are clear first!
You have to hold down the brake!
Huh?
S-sorry!
Hyraband Green!
I repent isn't nearly strong enough
to support this kind of weight.
You'll be torn to shreds.
Mr.
Joestar, with all due respect,
I am aware of my own abilities.
I am not a fool.
Ah, I get it.
You used the car's winch
instead of just brute strength.
Not bad, Kakyoin.
I got a question for you.
You like sumo?
Especially deadlocks at
the edge of the ring.
It's exciting, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm a fan of sumo.
But in sumo, it's against the
rules to punch your opponent.
Nothing here suggests
to use the stand attack.
I think it's safe to say he's just
some weirdo with an axe to grind.
Yeah, either way, he's
a goner after that fall.
I guess what goes around comes around.
Yeah, but I still wonder,
how did it get behind us?
It was like watching a
magician or something.
It's so strange.
Actually, little girl,
it's not strange at all.
The radio!
He's coming through the AM-FM!
I was able to do that because
it's my stand, Joestar! What?
He knows my name, so that confirms it.
He's an enemy stand user. Where is he?
Could he really be sending a
signal from the car down there?
No way!
Do you see the wreck down there?
No that old jalopy could
very well be a stand
you remember the boat
stand this may be a repeat.
Behold the wheel of fortune my
stand will lead you to your maker!
The wheel of fortune?
What the an earthquake I've got a
bad feeling everybody get in the car.
No stay back Don't go anywhere near it.
Couldn't be below us
Impossible!
It burrowed up to the ground!
Alright, I think it's pretty obvious
that car is actually a stand.
Looks like the stand's
user is inside the car.
What the hell?
Now what is it doing?
It's like it's alive!
It's heading straight for us!
If it's a duel you want,
I'm happy to oblige.
Don't do it, Jotaro!
Don't fight it yet!
Not until we know what
that Stan's power is!
Jotaro!
Impossible.
I couldn't see it.
What the hell did he shoot at
me, and how the hell did he...
Don't even know what hits you, huh?
You'll soon find out!
The moment you croak, that is!
Jotaro!
Jotaro! Hold her up! Kakyoin!
Goddamn!
What the hell is this?
The wounds aren't deep,
but they sting like hell!
I can't see it at all!
I thought the car threw something at us,
but there's nothing inside our wounds!
What the hell is going on here?
Jotaro, are you alright?
Don't worry about me, old man.
I don't know what the hell he's hurling
at us, but he's got damn good aim.
I'll pulverize your
legs so you can't move!
And then run you over!
Everyone, run between the boulders!
Stop running away, you coward!
What?
What are you, roaches?
Oh, no!
He's digging his way through!
And we're no match for him in here.
What a freak!
He's acting like some stupid muscle
head who got caught off in traffic?
and flew into a bit of road rage!
Just keep running!
Wait! Come back!
I can't keep up!
Yeah, okay, so I ran away from home!
I'm a good-for-nothing
drifter that nobody loves!
I'm gonna die!
Good grief.
If you have time to say all that crap,
you can run away, you damn little brat.
I love you so much, Jotaro!
Ha,
ha, ha, ha, go ahead and climb,
there's no path left for you to take,
no way to escape, no way to survive,
and last but certainly
not least, no future,
because this wheel of
fortune is going to grind you
into mid-speed and splatter
you all over these boulders,
I'll paint this mountain
red with your guts,
oh no, it's climbing up The cliff!
Is there anything this car can't do?
Good grief.
Looks like the time to fight him's now.
The rest of you stay back. He's mine.
Once he climbs up here, the
car's underside will be bare.
Then we'll see just how
strong this thing is.
I get it.
Once its underside's exposed,
we may be able to attack it.
You're pretty fast there,
Jojirou, but not too bright.
Your body's reeking, you
haven't even noticed.
Try paying attention.
Come to think of it, I
guess I did smell gasoline.
It's coming from us.
Our bodies smell like a gas station.
That's what it was shooting.
Gasoline.
It was shooting small amounts of
it at high speed, like bullets.
Double.
This is nuts!
So he wasn't trying to wound us.
He was dousing our bodies with gasoline.
We're covered in this stuff.
Looks like you finally caught
on, but it's too late now.
Now all you need is a little jolt.
Jotarou! Ah!
Ah!
Jotaro! Mr. Joestar! Stay back!
We're soaking with gasoline, too!
It's too dangerous! Ah!
Jotaro!
I win!
Your valiant hero finally bit the dust!
Is that so?
And who exactly would
replace me, Chotaro Cujo?
Let me guess.
You thought it'd be you, you roadhog.
You burrowed into the
ground with star platinum.
So the only thing that
burned up was your jacket.
A little parting wisdom what
you said earlier about paths?
Was dead wrong you see in life you have to
forge your own path no
one can do it for you!
So I'll offer you some guidance!
But first you have to go
through a little pain.
That is how it's done.
See, you just paved your own path.
Congrats on being a fast learner.
Here ends the lesson.
What an odd guy.
His arms are the size of boulders
and yet everything else is so small.
Talk about a bluff.
Hello.
Going somewhere?
Please don't kill me!
I'm just sinners for the money! Honest!
Oh, would you look at that?
I can't believe the stand was disguising
such a small car that entire time.
Kind of reminds me of a fluffy little sheep
that just had all of its wool shorn off.
What a pathetic hunk of junk.
Well, then, let's take
his car across the border.
Only fair since he smashed ours.
It's pretty beat up, though.
I wonder if it'll last that long.
Help! Help!
You're on the next flight to Hong
Kong once we find an airport.
Oh, no! Why? Shut up!
Don't you understand that you're
in the way, you little brat?
Er, we might not make it that far.
Seiko!
Seiko! Seiko!
Seiko! Seiko! Seiko! Seiko!
Seiko!
My seven assassins have all
been defeated, and so easily!
How could they be crushed
like that? The shame!
I cannot bear to face Lordeo.
Damn you!
Curse you, Polnareff!
Curse Kakyoin!
Curse Jotaro and his wretched grandfather!
I, Inyama, shall be your
next and final opponent!
I will fight with my very own
stand, the stand of justice!
All the old paintings on the tomb?
They do the sand dance, don't you know!
If they move too quick, oh well!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile!
You got the money on a bet!
Called crocodiles!
Oh-eh-oh!
Then I snap their teeth on your cigarette!
Falling tight to the hookah! I say!
Oh-eh-oh!
Walk like an Egyptian!
The blonde waitresses take their trays!
Spin around and they cross the floor!
They've got the moves!
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more!
All the school kids so sick of books!
They're like the punk and the metal band!
When the buzzer rings!
They're walking like an Egyptian!
All the kids in the marketplace say!
Walk
like
an Egyptian!
The fog looks thicker up ahead!
He's dead with that look of fear!
What is with the people in this town?
This is no ordinary murder!
The Joestar party is on the third floor!
Well hello!
I see you are traveling!
Ah salaam alaykum!